RG 062:122, Town of Salisbury
Connecticut State Library
Town of Salisbury records
1756-1935
Connecticut State Library
Salisbury (Conn.)
2.75 cubic feet
Administrative, school, military and land records for the town of Salisbury.
RG062_122
Multiple
Historical Note
The town of Salisbury was incorporated in October 1741.
Scope and Content
Administrative, school, military and land records for the town of Salisbury.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Deeds -- Connecticut -- Salisbury
Places:
Salisbury (Conn.) -- Records and correspondence
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Records, 1756-1935
  - T000285
    - Selectmen's reports, 1811-1839 (Box Box 1)
    - Highway records, 1818-1827 (Box Box 1)
    - Legal records, 1813, 1871 (Box Box 1)
    - School accounts, and school abatements, 1816-1880 (Box Box 1)
    - Fox bounty and sheep bounty records [Gift of Malcolm D. Rudd Estate], 1834-1865 (Box Box 1)
    - Town records, 1780-1838 (Box Box 1)
    - Highway records, 1759-1851 (Box Box 1)
    - Military records [Gift of Samuel Tanenbaum], 1851-1865 (Box Box 1)
    - Abatements lists, 1778-1784 (Box Box 1)
    - School tax list, 1896 (Box Box 2)
    - Historical notes from Salisbury Land records, town meeting records and grand lists, apparently taken by M. D. Rudd, circa 1882 (Box Box 2)
    - Assorted town records, undated (Box Box 2)
    - Index to family names in the second book of Salisbury vital records compiled by M. D. Rudd, 1913 (Box Box 2)
    - Town deeds, highway surveys, 1756-1820 (Box Box 2)
    - Deeds received for registration, 1760-1860 (Box Boxes 3-4)
  - 1984-007
    - Relief Financial Fund cards, 1933-1935 (Box Box 1)
  - 1993-014
    - Samuel Moore notes on surveying, 1805-1809 (Box Envelope)
      Purchased by Connecticut State Library on July 30, 1942 from H. A. Armstrong of New Haven
    - Moore, Samuel. An Accurate System of Surveying (Litchfield Conn.: T. Collier, 1796 ). (Box Envelope)
  - 2012-023
    - Ledger book, 1810-1813, 1874-1877 (Box Item 1)
      Entries on day's work, board, iron ore, wood, grain, road work.